(Sheldon:)Oh, yes. Over here.
(Howard:)You...
(Sheldon:)What are you doing now?
(Howard:)Making a straw.
(Sheldon:)Why?
(Howard:)So I can shoot you
with a spitball.
(Sheldon:)You're not going to do that,
and I'll tell you why.
(Sheldon:)This is an institution
of higher learning,
(Sheldon:)I am your professor,
(Sheldon:)and you're going to treat me
with the prop...
(gasps)
(Sheldon:)You shot your spit in my mouth!
(Howard:)Is that gonna be on the test?
(Howard:)Because I don't think
I can do that again.
(Amy(on phone):)Hey, girlfriend.
(Amy(on phone):)Can I get a what what?
(Leonard:)What?
(Amy:)Close enough.
(Amy:)Um, I was just calling to see
what you were up tonight.
(Amy:)Thought maybe we could hit up
Color Me Mine,
(Amy:)maybe sneak in
some Pinot Greej. Whatevs.
(Penny:)Uh, thanks, but I think
I'm gonna stay in
(Penny:)and go over the stuff
Bernadette gave me.
(Amy:)Oh. Oh, I hear you.